{
    "id": "499401f075b0475faecfb04117601b91",
    "title": "Common noun + preposition combinations",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b81dc90eb26242d58e6ea6286c043f66",
            "title": "Noun + Preposition Combinations",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We had little hope …………………. success nonetheless, we decided to perform the operation.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "about",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cash-for-vote scandal did a lot of harm …………………… his reputation as a conscientious politician.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have to find a substitute ……………………… it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We should deem it as an attack ……………………… our right to privacy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In many cities the cost …………………… living is pretty high.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We would like to see a big increase ………………….. productivity.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have no interest ……………………… politics.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have no faith ………………… her capabilities.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have heard that the government is planning to raise the tax …………………… automobiles.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "for",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I admire their way ………………… doing things.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "of",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}